<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bad Voltage</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org</link><description>Every two weeks Bad Voltage delivers an amusing take on technology, Open Source, politics, music, and anything else we think is interesting, as well as interviews and reviews. The show is presented by Jono Bacon, Jeremy Garcia, and Stuart Langridge.</description><copyright>Copyright © Bad Voltage 2016</copyright><pubDate>2019-07-16 15:31:59.472689020 +02:00</pubDate><image><url>http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3796/10457843775_fd9d126d53_o.jpg</url><title></title><link></link></image><item><title>2×55: Moaner Lisa</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/07/12/2x55/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which the Mona Lisa is bobbins, it is important to have your privacy policy meet the overall goals you’re pushing, and:


    [00:01:00] There’s a new site launched calling for a ban on facial recognition. Should it be banned...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/5dda27a2c14b514ab73f5e5c7342f664.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 09:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×54: Well Baffled</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/06/27/2x54/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we only get the bad bits of Neuromancer, apparently “stank” is a noun, and:


    [00:01:13] More and more companies are going for some sort of “open core” business model approach to software distribution: parts of the ...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x54.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×53: The Route of All Evil</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/06/13/2x53/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which Stuart gets the episode number wrong, the ghosts of KWebStat and Jokosher are unearthed, and:


    [00:01:52] Github Sponsors: a new donations programme from Github where people can give money to support an open source...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x53.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 12:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×52: Apples to Oranges</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/05/16/2x52/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which there is charity and there is hope but there is not a lot of faith, and:


    [00:02:50] Lenovo are apparently making a Thinkpad-brand foldable PC next year. We have Thoughts, not surprisingly
    [00:08:40] Uber final...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x52.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 12:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×51: Game of Groans</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/04/18/2x51/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and special guest presenter Jorge Castro present Bad Voltage, in which apparently reading A Song of Ice and Fire is as bad as being a Crossfit person or using Arch, Jorge refuses to publicly state just how many HDMI devices he has, and:


    [00:02:30] The Sony Play...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x51.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×50: Born In A Log Cabin</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/03/21/2x50/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which Jono is at death’s door and not present, Stuart mixes the show and therefore any complaints should be directed to him (and obviously these will make Jono feel good about himself), and:


    [00:1:20] A short review of SCaLE17x and ...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x50.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 17:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×49: Social Missiles</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/02/21/2x49/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we declare a moratorium on social media, there is Tinder but for livestock, and:


    [00:03:00] Google may be killing the back button in Android Q
    [00:10:40] Project Alias: block your home assistant from listening...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x49.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 10:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×48: Antisocial Media</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/02/14/2x48/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we take ourselves up on a challenge we set a couple of episodes ago.

Social media. There’s pretty wide agreement that there are issues with it; that it fosters divisiveness and a lack of nuance, it amplifies the narcis...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x48.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×47: Get Oval Shortbread</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/02/07/2x47/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge and Jeremy Garcia present an abbreviated Bad Voltage, in the lead up to Bad Voltage Live at SCaLE in Pasadena, California on March 8th! With some thoughts on what makes a good conference, some confusion as to what the hell Essential are doing releasing a paid-for email app, and a...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x47.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 12:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×46: A Giant Loser</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/01/24/2x46/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we look forward for the year and describe what we think will happen in tech in 2019! Our predictions are:


    Jono:
        
            These companies will IPO: Uber (the largest IPO ever), Peloton, Lyft, Slack, Clo...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x46.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×45: Volt 45</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2019/01/10/2x45/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we look back on our predictions for 2018 and see how we did. Not wishing to give anything away, but if you were expecting clairvoyant genius… you might want to tone down your hopes a bit.

And in a real prediction of so...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x45.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 18:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×44: Seven Systems</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/12/13/2x44/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which there are more rants than expected, there are seven seconds of panic, and:


    [00:02:00] Google drop the latest on Messages, Allo, Duo and Hangouts, where “the latest” is “we’re cancelling Allo”, which both people on...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x44.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 21:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×43: Shouting and shaming</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/11/29/2x43/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and special guest Alan Pope standing in for Jeremy present Bad Voltage, in which Tiger Tokens are a more viable currency than you think, AI gets things wrong again, and:


    [00:02:20] A popular open source dependency in use by many packages, with two million weekl...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x43.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:22:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×42: The Book 2024</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/11/13/2x42/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which the show was recorded in slightly unusual circumstances because people are travelling at our normal time, phones are now literally twice as big as they ought to be if you like tiny phones which apparently nobody does, a...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x42.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×41: To Star Repeat 5 Forward 100 Right 144</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/11/02/2x41/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which a proof through poetry is presented and utterly fails to move the audience, Red Hat maintains a ton of things, and:


    [00:01:20] IBM acquires Red Hat; let the hot takes begin
    [00:24:30] Microsoft deal to acquire...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x41.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×40: Teeth Will Be Provided</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/10/18/2x40/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which we appeal for Colgate corporate sponsorship, nobody adds a fake notch, and:


    [00:01:30] Google release the Pixel 3 phone and Pixel Slate ChromeOS tablet/laptop, with no surprises given all the press leaks ahead of ...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x40.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2×39: Snark of the Covenant</title><link>https://www.badvoltage.org/2018/09/27/2x39/</link><description><![CDATA[Stuart Langridge, Jono Bacon, and Jeremy Garcia present Bad Voltage, in which the hardest part of being a developer is personal development, the BV team average two-thirds of a workout per day, and:


    [00:02:10] Apple release the Apple Watch 4 with a bunch of health additions, and iOS 12 is a...]]></description><author>Bad Voltage</author><enclosure url="http://audio.lugradio.org/badvoltage/Bad%20Voltage%202x39.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>