<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Talking Machines</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description>Talking Machines is your window into the world of machine learning. Your hosts, Katherine Gorman and Neil Lawrence, bring you clear conversations with experts in the field, insightful discussions of industry news, and useful answers to your questions.  Machine learning is changing the questions we can ask of the world around us, here we explore how to ask the best questions and what  to do with the answers.</description><pubDate>2019-07-11 00:28:38.468929129 +02:00</pubDate><image><url>https://content.production.cdn.art19.com/images/44/39/e9/68/4439e968-d3f7-48c2-8158-146c43a73426/1aebbf35ec5a7850cf308d730985ca70135e8b2392cc3028a8350a67c9cc9c583a91ccfeb90b6cdb57244727903fad715d2acf79eea0268affedff4f68283592.jpeg</url><title></title><link></link></image><item><title>The View from Addis Ababa</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode thirteen of season five we bring you a the rest of our conversation with Michael Melese from Addis Ababa University and Charles Saidu of Baze University Abuja]]></description><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/3400fae1000898df449b408b680886b2.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>DSA Addis Ababa and ICML Los Angeles</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode twelve of season five we bring you a rundown of Data Science Africa's latest workshop answer a listener question about what got us excited at ICML and hear the first part of our conversation with Michael Melese from Addis Ababa University and Charles Saidu of Baze University Abuja]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/f49c55f6-c745-4240-81be-20d2c7bd6927.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Trusts and Citation Trends</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode eleven of season five, we dig in to just what a data trust actually is, take a look at citation trends and other places (PMLR) you can dig up data to understand the field and talk with  Raia Hadsell of DeepMind.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/f2397096-4168-4d06-bf4e-b4cdcb0851a1.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 23:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reproducibly and Revisiting History</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode ten of season five we talk about reproducibility, take a listener question on re understanding the history of the field given where we are now  and how other fields are reviewing their own history and listen to a conversation with Graham Taylor of the Vector Institute.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/a5713ee2-cf48-4eeb-b4c9-761e7de2c4ef.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Insights from AISTATS</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode nine of season five we talk about some interesting work from AISTATS, dive into unbiased implicit variational inference, and chat with Jon McAuliffe CIO of Voleon]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/cd27ff05-7090-4414-9466-2f3ea897acdc.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 02:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Deep End of Deep Learning</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In this episode as we prep for ICLR we take a break from our usual format to bring you a talk from Hugo LaRochelle at TedX Boston on Deep Learning.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/210ed7ae-1c31-48dd-a9ce-d3d44ae37eba.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 22:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring MARS and Getting back to Bayesics</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode seven of season five of we chat about MARS and Re: MARS OpenAI's status changes and We talk with Jasper Snoek of Google Brain]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/a099a7b1-8214-411e-a539-061153defcf7.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sweetness of a Bitter Lesson and Bringing ML and Healthcare Closer</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode six of season five we talk about Richard Sutton's A Bitter Lesson. Chat about IEEE's new Ethical Guidelines  and talk with Andrew Beam Senior Fellownn at Flagship Pioneering, Head of Machine Learning for Flagship VL57 and Assistant Professor, Department of Epidemiology, Harvard T.H. Ch...]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/03cf6eae-2fd8-4c9e-8da2-03fcf467f59d.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 21:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Slowed Down Conferences and Even More Summer Schools</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode five of season five we talk about the Stu Hunter conference, Summer schools options (DLRLSS!) and chat with Adrian Weller of the Alan Turing Institute]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/109b18a1-3985-4978-bd2c-e02ee291afa3.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jupyter Notebooks and Modern Model Distribution</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode four of season five we talk about Jupyter Notebooks and Neil's dream of a world craft software and devices, we take a listener question about the conversation surrounding Open AI's GPT-2 its announcement and the coverage and we hear an interview with Brooks Paige of the Alan Turing Ins...]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/ba79334d-1359-409e-b047-469a4f30c8ec.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Real World Real Time and Five Papers for Mike Tipping</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In season five episode three we chat about take a listener question about Five Papers for Mike Tipping, take a listener question on AIAI and chat with Eoin O'Mahony of Uber




Here are Neil's five papers. What are yours?

Stochastic variational inference by Hoffman, Wang, Blei and Paisley

http:...]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/aae7c113-dfa3-4200-a16b-a23ba33ff1a1.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 01:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bezos Paradox and Machine Learning Languages</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode two of season five we unpack the Bezos Paradox (TM Neil Lawrence) take a listener question about best papers and chat with Dougal Maclaurin of Google Brain.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/bc7696f7-5972-484d-8c6a-86947f0f23df.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Being Global Bit by Bit</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode one of season five we talk about Bit by Bit, take a listener question on machine learning gatherings on the African continent (Deep Learning INDABA! DSA!) and hear an interview with Daphne Koller recorded at ODSC West]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/6f6e5a9e-3cab-4219-81dc-49bda1676cae.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 23:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Possibility Of Explanation and The End of Season Four</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[For the end of season four we take a break from our regular format and bring you a talk from Professor Finale Doshi Velez of Harvard University on the possibility of explanation Tune in next season!]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/8917ad7f-1311-4485-b4cd-5741d5bed60e.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Neural Information Processing Systems and Distributed Internal Intelligence Systems</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode twenty one of season four we talk about distributed intelligence systems (mainly those internal to humans), talk about what were excited to see at the Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems and in advance of our trek to Canada we chat with Garth Gibson president and CEO of...]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/36b25e8a-5698-434c-a680-e1ee17d89bbe.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Driven Ideas and Actionable Privacy</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode twenty of season four we talk about the importance of crediting your data, answer a listener question about internships vs salaried positions and talk with Matt Kusner of the Alan Turing institute  the UK’s national institute for data science and AI.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/52fdf40f-aa72-4c1b-8b02-fb8cd10e30bf.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI for Good and The Real World</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode nineteen of season four we talk about causality in the real world, take a question about being surprised by the elephant in the room and talk with Kush Varshney of IBM.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/1ae8f3dc-7e4b-474e-aeb4-91dc2c6d19b8.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Systems Design and Tools for Transparency</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 18 of season four we talk about systems design, (remember the 3 d's!), tools for transparency and fairness and we talk with Adria Gascon of The Alan Turing Institute, the UK’s national institute for data science and AI.]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/5822211d-b2dd-449e-8500-5374e58c83d3.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Research in Hype and CIFAR&apos;s Strategy</title><link>https://art19.com/shows/talking-machines</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 17 of season four we talk about how to research in a time of hype (and other lessons from Tom Griffiths book) Neil's love of variational methods, and with Chat with Elissa Strome director of the Pan-Canadian AI Strategy for CIFAR]]></description><enclosure url="https://rss.art19.com/episodes/d8f92204-70c0-4deb-a37f-c4f1cc92c3cd.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>