<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Daily Zeitgeist</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description>There’s more news and less comprehension today than any historical period that didn’t involve literal witch trials, and trying to stay on top of it all can feel like playing a game of telephone with 30 people, except everyone’s speaking at the same time and like a third of them are openly racist for some reason. From Cracked co-founder Jack O’Brien, THE DAILY ZEITGEIST is stepping into that fray with some of the funniest and smartest comedic and journalistic minds around. Jack and co-host Miles Gray spend up to an hour every weekday sorting through the events and stories driving the headlines, to help you find the signal in the noise, with a few laughs thrown in for free.</description><copyright>Copyright 2017 HowStuffWorks.com</copyright><pubDate>2019-07-04 09:15:09.773975200 +02:00</pubDate><image><url>https://static.megaphone.fm/podcasts/052418f4-2d44-11e8-805b-9780d43c8144/image/uploads_2F1547068953681-q867wqaqx9k-7b04f1ac53cb97a3046963b69adc8b76_2FTheDailyZeitgeist-Logo-iHR-FINAL-3000x3000.jpg</url><title></title><link></link></image><item><title>Renner Or Not, Here He Comes; Spicy Snack Matrix 7.3.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 426, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Chris Crofton to discuss where the popular 2020 candidates are in the polls, Fox &amp; Friends defending the border patrol, a look at Jeremy Renner's musical work, a spicy snack power ranking list, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES:<br><br>1. <a hre...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/42d05b39e8a2355cf7e66b69fcdbf285.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Twilight’ The Rollercoaster? Joe “Woke Joke” Biden 7.2.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 425, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Charla Lauriston to discuss Trump meeting with Kim Jong Un, Joe Biden sharing his classic 'woke' anecdote, a check in with the crowdfunded border wall, JNCO jeans coming back, Lionsgate opening a theme park in China, why weather forecasting is...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/5ebc1cba29ce645c34937a68c6b0713d.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Debate Winners And Bidens, Finally A Day For Straight Men 7.1.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 424, Jack and special guest host Caitlin Durante are joined by Sleepwalkers podcast co-host Karah Preiss to discuss Twitter playing right into Trump's hands, Democratic polls after the debates, Boston approving a straight white parade, New York declaring a climate emergency, and more! ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/7df03fb68b854875ec1cb2a19d8c2afd.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 81 (Best of 6/24/19-6/28/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 88 (6/24/19-6/28/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/d95614bd86ba7e941da9e0827c5bcd1b.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Debate Reactions, Cocaine: Don&apos;t Call It A Comeback 6.28.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 423, Jack and special guest host Sara June are joined by comedian and Bechdel Cast co-host Jamie Loftus to discuss the Taco Bell hotel selling out in two minutes, a new Subway ad, the Democratic debates, The Office leaving Netflix, cocaine being BACK, and more! <br><br>NOTE FROM SARA: ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/b9efdf15f78a918e03c3b585d2a8cc85.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim K Can Close Her Kimono, Mueller To Open His? 6.27.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 422, Jack and special guest host super producer Nick Stumpf are joined by Creature Feature podcast host Katie Goldin to discuss the controversial name for Kim Kardashians new shape wear, Trump making a joke about McCain's death, Robert Mueller planning to testify before the House Judic...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/938e714f88c93747cb02ab6f507d6efb.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Dance Off! ‘Euphoria’ Too Hot For Real Teens 6.26.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 421, Jack and special guest host Daniel Van Kirk are joined by Ridiculous History podcast's Noel Brown to discuss break dancing being provisionally approved for Paris 2024, the media 'Trump slump,' rape accusations against Trump going unnoticed, Trump's verbal attack on Iran, NCAA refu...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/6a505d90a78ab0ddfc19650a001e331b.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Toy Story 4 Too Woke? Oregon Too Much Weed? 6.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 420, Jack and special guest host Sara June are joined by comedian drag queen and Ghosted podcast host Roz Drezfalez to discuss how Oregon has way too much weed, Warner Bro's Media hiring a female CEO, the US military thinking we can win a nuclear win, Pete Buttigieg facing criticism fr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/16fcd01aa1569afc89888b4c771d617b.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Are The Beatles Cool? Trump’s Hollywood Star Is A Lie 6.24.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 419, Jack and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian Tiff Stevenson to discuss some Bachelorette drama with super producer Anna Hossnieh, how the Dominican Republic is canceled, a new member of the hundred billion club, the new scammer in charge of the Department of Tran...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/0f42a65e547cb596b22592ce5b4a8cbf.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 80 (Best of 6/17/19-6/21/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 87 (6/17/19-6/21/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/25c910a15c6998d0210f5ef319a3a8b9.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Young People Growing Horns, GTFO Biden 6.21.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 418, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Bechdel Cast co-host Caitlin Durante to discuss young people growing horns, Iran shooting down a US drone, Joe Biden losing his mind, more on problematic behavior by Tony Robbins, the Jamba Juice Sicko Mode remix, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOT...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/b3a05fae89f58752a272c1614ea5fe30.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>More Like Concentration Spas, AirPod Sex = A Thing 6.20.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 417, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian JC Coccoli to discuss Trump starting his 2020 campaign, the Trump administrations thoughts on reparations, the comparison of concentration camps to migrant detention centers, music's influence on sexual behavior, Russia remaking the Chernobyl ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/7d2ca7511e114ac38822d37e5428eace.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>At Home Racist, OJ Just OJ&apos;n 6.19.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 416, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Legally Insane podcast co-host Tony Sam to discuss Menghazi with Max Landis and Cuba Gooding Jr., Trump slowly losing his people, OJ Simpson threatening to cut people on Twitter, Kyle Kashuv's Harvard admission being rescinded, and more! <...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/0ffed24b0e729cb70427163e157bc07b.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SHOCKER: YouTube is Evil, OJ is on Twitter?? 6.18.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 415, Jack and special guest host Billy Wayne Davis are joined by comedian Mano Again to discuss YouTube trying to fix their algorithm, Democrats embarrassing themselves on Twitter, a weird video from Garth Brooks, people who shouldn't be on social media including OJ Simpson and Bill Co...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://cdn.staticaly.com/gh/gareins/sp3/audio/audio/0b69e7910464703d26c3f3cca4557845.ogg" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Air Bud Is GOAT, New Shaft = Old Shaft 6.17.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 414, Jack and Miles are joined by I'm Too Effing High podcast's James Mastraieni to discuss Toronto Raptors winning the NBA championship, whether or not Airbud was actually good at basketball, Elizabeth Warren surging in California, Cuba Gooding Jr turning himself in for groping a woma...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7651538595.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 79 (Best of 6/10/19-6/14/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 86 (6/10/19-6/14/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7609643645.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Keanu’s Reevesurgence: We’re All Witnesses, Bye Sarah 6.14.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 413, Jack and Miles are joined by writer and performer Rachel Wenitsky to discuss the Keanu Reevesurgence, the 'Tiger Mom' who supported Brett Kavanaugh, Michael Flynn angling for a pardon, Sarah Huckabee Sanders leaving the White House, the office of the special council recommending K...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9033060987.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chernobyl Selfies R Hot, Trump Hearts Rihanna 6.13.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 412, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Ellory Smith to discuss selfies at disaster zones, Trump saluting Rihanna, the Global Peace Index of 2019, 2020 polls numbers, why millennial consumers aren't that great, stories from the Radiohead <em>OK Computer</em> sessions leak, the new M...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5650453274.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Avengers: Endgame’ Killed X-Men, NRA Robs Self At Gunpoint 6.12.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 411, Jack and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian and Bechdel Cast co-host Jamie Loftus to discuss the shooting of David 'Big Papi' Ortiz in the Dominican Republic, the NRA stealing money from themselves, suicides by gun, Trump's tariff's deal for Mexico, Walmart intr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8206174717.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bieber vs Cruise … But Like, WHY? Stalin So Hot Right Now 6.11.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 410, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Eric Lampaert to discuss the new Jamba Juice, Justin Bieber challenging Tom Cruise, people pretending to be black on the internet in the worse way, Beto not doing so hot, a story about Kawhi Leonard and apples, a video game wrap up, and more! ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3452662339.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Perfect ClickBait, No Place Like Clone 6.10.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 409, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian and Las Culturistas co-host Matt Rogers to discuss Nancy Pelosi delaying a Trump impeachment, The Intercept's Ryan Grim's new book about the Bret Kavanaugh hearings, Barbara Streisand posting photos of her clone dogs...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8212458852.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 78 (Best of 6/3/19-6/7/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 85 (6/3/19-6/7/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1458665007.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Downey = Tony Stark, Just Admit You’re Evil 6.7.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 408, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian Daniel Van Kirk to discuss Robert Downey Jr. turning into Iron Man, the trade wars with Mexico, the Trump administration cutting funding that gives migrant children basic rights, the straight pride parade, the new X-...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7660525976.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apocalypse 2050, PUNK’D? Again? 6.5.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 406, Jack and Miles are joined by poet Melissa Lozada-Oliva to discuss Ivanka and John Bolton being booed in the UK, if internet shutdowns are safe, Nancy Pelosi playing 9-D chess, if town halls are helping the 2020 presidential candidates, MTV bringing back <em>Singled Out</em> and <e...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3896402021.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 12:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Poop Like A Jedi, KushNO GO AWAY 6.4.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 405, Jack and Miles are joined by Yo Is This Racist's Andrew Ti to discuss the new IHOB roll out, Trump in the UK and his new hairstyle, Jared Kushner's Axios interview, movie studios threatening to leave Georgia over their abortion laws, Disneyland's new <em>Star Wars: Galaxy Edge</em...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7798387442.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 77 (Best of 5/27/19-5/31/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 84 (5/27/19-5/31/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5147826151.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen Z &gt; Millennials At Voting, Arnold &gt; Kendrick? 5.31.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 403, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Maggie Maye to discuss Moby canceling his book tour, younger generations outvoting older generations, freedom gas, Trump claiming Russia did not help get elected, the Democrats needing to impeach Trump, La Croix fading away, Arnold Schwarzeneg...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3836368365.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mueller He Spoke, Believe Sci-Fi Writers</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 402, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Lady to Lady podcast's Barbara Grey to discuss Alex Trebek's cancer, IHOP changing its name to IHOP, Robert Mueller speaking out finally about Trump, Elizabeth Warren being the most popular among liberals, why we should listen to sci-fi-fi...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2474337651.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky TicTac 2020; Hey Alexa, Perpetuate Patriarchy 5.29.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 401, Jack and Miles are joined by our favorite Jamie Loftus to discuss female voice assistants that are furthering gender stereotypes, the New York Times article about aliens, Harriet Tubman at the twenty dollar bill, the Trump administration attacking climate science, the mysterious H...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4745308063.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>King Of The Baby Filter, Pelosi Not Drunk But Deserves To Be 5.28.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 400, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and activist Derrick Lemos to discuss the <em>Sonic the Hedgehog</em> film being pushed back, the new <em>Between Two Ferns</em> film, more on Tony Robbins shady behavior, Trump and his team coming for Nancy Pelosi, William Barr investigating ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9385266979.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 76 (Best of 5/20/19-5/24/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 83 (5/20/19-5/24/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1812208083.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bye, Moby; Wish In One Hand... 5.24.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 399, Jack and Miles are joined by Creature Feature podcast host Katie Goldin to discuss Moby creeping on Natalie Portman, a Buzzfeed report on sexual misconduct by Tony Robbins, Russian documents revealing desire to manufacture a race war in the US, everyone's different pooping habits,...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5286013536.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>New Coke, Who Dis? No Justice, No Infrastructure 5.23.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 398, Jack and Miles are joined by singer-songwriter and host of the Peace Of Mind Podcast Bhi Bhiman to discuss the return of New Coke, Hope Hicks and more being subpoenaed, the release of the new Aladdin movie, who your cartoon crush was, Christopher Nolan's new movie, Chris Broussard...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9389392142.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wick Is Sick, What Happened To My Husband? 5.22.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 397, Jack and Miles are joined by journalist and author Amy Westervelt to discuss Guy Fieri’s hair causing STRESS, the new season of Real World, ‘Born in the USA’ isn’t actually what you think it is, Joe Biden, Trump hating on Fox, Trump hating on Clean Air, John Wick, Detective Pikach...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8143255146.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Republican “Gets It”? You’ve GoT To Be Kidding 5.21.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 396, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Brooke Van Poppelen to discuss Arnold Schwarzenegger being kicked in South Africa, Justin Amash finally finishing up reading the Mueller Report, Trump being angry at Fox News for covering presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg, Game of Thrones ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6327248154.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>QAnon vs. Butterflies, RIP Grumpy Cat 5.20.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 395, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Blake Wexler to discuss Grumpy Cat passing away, Robert Pattinson playing Batman, William Barr threatening democrats and more interesting revelations from the Mueller Report, QAnon ruining a cities earth day celebration, Rudy Giuliani doing mo...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1997869017.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 75 (Best of 5/13/19-5/17/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 82 (5/13/19-5/17/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1587867651.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wicked Sexy Boston, Taco Bell: The Hotel 5.17.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 394, Jack and Miles are joined by Go Fact Yourself co-host J. Keith van Straaten to discuss the sexiest accents in the US, more on what is going on with the abortion bills in south, Game of Thrones fan theories, the new Taco Bell hotel, McDonalds teaming up with US Embassies, Chris Roc...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8743445176.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Leave Britney Alone? Shade of Thrones 5.16.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 393, Miles and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by singer, activist, actress and world famous Drag Queen DJ Pierce aka Shangela to discuss a father scamming the police, iPhone users possibly being able to sue Apple, Elizabeth Warren coming for Fox News, Alabama basically banni...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4567474838.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Very Dark Game, Old Phone What’s Dis? 5.14.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 391, Jack and Miles are joined by Teen Creeps co-host Kelly Nugent to discuss a video of millennials trying to use a rotary phone, celebrity naval cheese, the escalation of trade wars, how the GoFundMe for the wall was a scam, the end of the Sixers season, Game of Throne baby names, an...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7308625625.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift = Night King? SHAPIRO PWNED BY THE RIGHT 5.13.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 390, Jack and Miles are joined by the Inside Conan podcast hosts Jessie Gaskell and Mike Sweeney to discuss the Natty Light college internship, Ben Shapiro's meltdown on BBC, the new conservative Daily Show, an analysis of Mike Huckabee's 'best jokes,'&nbsp; Hollywood coming for Georgi...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4632753035.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 74 (Best of 5/6/19-5/10/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 81 (5/6/19-5/10/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2555958431.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CannaBLISS, Rights?! LOL 5.10.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 389, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Recently Added podcast co-host Nick Turner to discuss the decriminalization of psychedelic mushrooms in Denver, how marijuana can help your relationship, six states new heartbeat bills, China's persecution of the Uighur population and thei...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8255312497.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Good with Powers Of Extortion, Greatest Lo$er 5.9.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 388, Jack and Miles are joined by trans supermodel, actress, and comedian Arisce Wanzer to discuss the new royal baby's name, the new Watchmen show on HBO, the Sultan of Brunei backing down on his gay sex death penalty, Trump's tax returns showing over a billion in losses, Trump claims...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6215006349.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pokemoneurology, Sharing Is Winning 5.8.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 387, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss the "Pokemon" region of the brain, how sharing food leads to successful negotiations, Trump asking for a late check out, the birth of the Royal baby, the Met Gala, Woodstock 50, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES:<br><br>...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2687631087.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bird Scoot Or Die, Amazon: Hello Cruel World 5.7.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 386, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Yusef Roach to discuss everyone going to the same prison, the House moving to hold William Barr in contempt, where the best jobs are if you do not have a college degree, Amazon marketing to our fear, head injuries from e-scooters increasing, B...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1829936717.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lit(erary) Gifts, UFOs Are So In 5.6.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 385, Jack and Miles are joined by comic artist Kim Winder to discuss which scam you are based on your sign, Bill and Chelsea Clinton's new podcast, how angry pilots for the Navy to stop dismissing possible UFO sightings, Elizabeth Warren coming out with a plan for debt relief in Puerto...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3811730918.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 73 (Best of 4/29/19-5/3/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 80 (4/29/19-5/3/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6575884042.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Tried, Xenu’s Measles Yacht 5.3.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 384, Jack and Miles are joined by Natch Beaut's Jackie Johnson to discuss Taylor Swift's Billboard Music Awards performance, a Scientology cruise chip being quarantined over a case of the measles, William Barr ditching the House Judiciary Committee hearing, the salary you need to make ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4409700366.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mad Mueller, Guac Cheese? 5.2.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 383, Jack and Miles are joined by QAnon Anonymous Podcast's Julian Feeld to discuss guac cheese, the cancellation of Woodstock 50, William Barr being shady in front of the Senate Judiciary Committee, what is going on in the QAnon world, Fed reserve nominee Stephen Moore making racist j...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2667378113.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonic The WRETCH Hog, You’re Welcome McDonald’s 5.1.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 382, Jack and Miles are joined by Stuff They Don't Want You To Know and Ridiculous History's Ben Bowlin to discuss John Singleton's career, McDonalds sales jumping 4.5% since unveiling bacon, the Poway synagogue shooting, Biden's new campaign ad, GOP attacking socialism for not helping...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5866754044.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s The Endgame Of The World, Trump’s Terrifying Anti-Vax Beliefs 4.29.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 380, Jack and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian and Private Parts Unknown co-host Courtney Kocak to discuss the Avengers: Endgame box office sales, Kanye West's Sunday Service, Britney Spears coming back home, a possible herpes outbreak at Coachella, a measles outbr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5405967021.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 72 (Best of 4/22/19-4/26/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 79 (4/22/19-4/26/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7106410925.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Let The Endgames Begin, GoT Death Pools 4.26.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 379, Jack and and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by pop culture critic Joelle Monique to discuss the Game Of Thrones death pool, if Prince William is cheating on Kate, Joe Biden officially announcing his presidency, the fall out from the Mueller Report, if Netflix is killin...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3022076640.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Debtflix, Protective Privilege 4.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 378, Miles is joined by Yo! Is This Racist? host Andrew Ti and comedian Steve Hernandez&nbsp; to discuss Steve King thinking he's holy or something, Herman Cain being too rich for his new job, Twitter users being the wokest, Donald Trump asking Twitter's Jack Dorsey "Where are my follo...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2474912761.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren’s War On Debt, Soft Boyzzz 4.23.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 376, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and V Single podcast co-host Alison Stevenson to discuss Beyonce's Netflix deal, the world's most hacked passwords, which celebrity donated to which presidential candidate, the Mueller Report hurting Trump's poll numbers, Elizabeth Warren's pl...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2200377721.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Worst Mueller Report Take, WT Actual F Ancestry.com? 4.22.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 375, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Nerdificent podcast co-host Ify Nwadiwe to discuss MoviePass losing most of its users, a new racist Ancestry.com ad, Lil Dicky's new viral video, the Game of Thrones soundtracking sounding similar to the Black Panther soundtrack, hot takes...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4349259472.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 71 (Best of 4/15/19-4/19/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 78 (4/15/19-4/19/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1444254302.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Mueller’s Report, Who Run The World (Netflix) 4.19.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 374, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Alyssa Sabo to discuss why Beyoncé went to Netflix, a LOT about the heavily-redacted Mueller report, Flint getting a glimmer of hope, AMI selling the National Enquirer, and more!<br><br>FOOTNOTES:<br><br>1. <a href="https://www.vulture.com/201...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9070223938.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>High Off Burgers, Tucker Carlson: Forever Gross 4.18.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 373, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Nerdificent co-host Dani Fernandez to discuss Carl's Jr. new CBD Burger, Beyonce's Coachella documentary and album drop, Mayor Pete making Tucker Carlson...hungry, Roy Moore leading the polls in Alabama, anti-semitic coffee shop owners, th...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4587022317.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Snow: F*** UR Feelings, Bernie Stuns Fox News 4.17.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 372, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Amy Miller to discuss the 2019 Box Office thus far, what’s coming to save Hollywood's ass, Bernie's Town Hall on Fox News, the young women in Congress owning Conservatives, the White House staff freaking out over the Mueller report, how to mak...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4821837001.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Firstporn Son, Piracy Is Coming 4.16.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 371, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Brandie Posey to discuss Notre Dame Cathedral, the Lion King remake and what that means for it's original writers and animators, Trump continuing to distract from the real issues, Democrats failing to defend Ilhan Omar, a man suing his parents...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4496525113.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Influencer Tears, Rise of WHICH Skywalker? 4.15.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 370, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Katia Kvinge to discuss Kim Kardashian studying to be a lawyer, the new Star Wars teaser, the problematic scene in Meet Joe Black, William Barr being shady, Trump describing his children, a Wisconsin restaurant banning middle schoolers, influe...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2733961234.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 70 (Best of 4/8/19-4/12/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 77 (4/8/19-4/12/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9842895565.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Old Pope, Old Takes; No, YOU’RE The Losers 4.12.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 369, Miles special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian Caitlin Gill to discuss Pope Benedict blaming the LGBTQ community for Catholicism’s problems, Julian Assange being charged by the US, the GOP putting AOC and Ilhan Omar in danger, the new Governor of Florida actually cari...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3988650787.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Black Hole, Fun? Game Of Thrones Already Won 4.11.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 368, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Punch Up The Jam's co-host Miel Bredouw to discuss the first photograph of a black hole, yogurt sales going down, Bernie's medicare for all bill, the anti-abortion movie dropping, Trump using Batman music without permission, how the Game o...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3036522160.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Prison Becky, Trampoline Parks UNSAFE? 4.10.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 367, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Lydia Popovich to discuss trampoline parks being unsafe, thank you emails after an job interview, Candace Owens claiming white nationalism isn't a thing, Ilhan Omar being called anti-semitic again for pointing out that Stephen Miller is a whit...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4972873645.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>L8R Reichstag Barbie, No WAY We’re Bad At Kissing 4.9.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 366, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Sofiya Alexandra to discuss how to banish telemarketers from calling you, Modern Monetary Theory, Trump picking Herman Cain to run the Federal Reserve, Kirstjen Nielsen resigning as Homeland Security Secretary, how the Dunning Kruger Effect is...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6207196089.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>New Old Town Road, IRS BFFs 4.8.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 365, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Zahra Noorbakhsh to discuss the 25th anniversary of Kurt Cobain's death, Game of Thrones branding everywhere, presidential taxes, Joe Biden's weak apology, the Lil Nas X featuring Billy Ray Cyrus Old Town Road remix, Lori Loughlin's daughter h...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1133397348.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 69 (Best of 4/1/19-4/5/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 76 (4/1/19-4/5/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2018940373.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Second String Spies? Mueller&apos;s Mad Men 4.5.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 364, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Johnny Pemberton to discuss how Lori Loughlin and Felicity Huffman possibly going to jail, Fox New's diner segment on the Green New Deal, Vic Berger's super cut of Joe Biden touching people, the Mueller Report being more damaging than William ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4621201892.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chem Sex? You&apos;re Too Close, Joe 4.3.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 362, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian, Bechdel Cast co-host, and frequent podcast host Jamie Loftus to discuss a "chemsex" study, more coming out about Joe Biden invading people's personal space, how authoritarians are bad at politics, Trump's approval rating not going up after th...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8805231225.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Skrillex vs Mosquitoes, Bezos vs Saudi Arabia 4.2.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 361, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jena Friedman to discuss April fool's jokes from different brand, Trump doubling down on his threat to close the border, allegations against Joe Biden, how Saudi Arabia hacked Jeff Bezo's phone, Skrillex protecting us from mosquitos, PewDiePie...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6606668218.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 68 (Best of 3/25/19-3/29/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 75 (3/25/19-3/29/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7853230386.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alexa, How Will I Die? Post-Barr Pre-Mueller World 3.29.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 359, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and <em>They Tried To Bury Us </em>podcast co-host Tamer Kattan to discuss AI predicting death accurately, why we were skinnier in the 80's, what we will be doing differently since the Mueller Report, Billboard deciding Lil Nas X isn't country...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9103025126.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cruella DeVos, Throne ‘n Bone 3.28.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 358, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Ryan Singer to discuss OK Cupid adding a Game Of Thrones feature, the evil Betsy DeVos trying to cut Special Olympics program, Purdue Pharma and the Sackler Family paying a settlement opioid crisis, what. to do with all the left over 'Mueller ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3650898327.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lord Beer Our Prayer, Exoneration Nation 3.27.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 357, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and scam goddess Laci Mosley to discuss The Sun tabloids coming for A-Rod, Jussie Smollett's charges being dropped, Trump trying to kill Obamacare, a suburb in New York banning unvaccinated children from the public, when to expect the public v...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7209055218.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>William Barr’s “The Mueller Report”, All Apple Everything 3.26.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 356, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Throwing Shade co-host Bryan Safi to discuss all the new Apple products, Stacey Abrams comments on being Joe Biden's running mate, Michael Avenatti being charged with extortion, the Mueller report as interpreted by William Barr, Scary Spac...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1486734563.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The SPECIAL Mueller Report Summary Report 3.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In this SPECIAL bonus episode, Jack and Miles are joined by super producers Anna Hossnieh and Nick Stumpf to break down what they know and understand about the Barr summary of Mueller's report. <br><br>FOOTNOTES: <br><br>1. <a href="https://twitter.com/SethAbramson/status/1109913558333210629">(TH...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6553238035.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mueller Hands In Homework, Papa Shaq&apos;s Pizza 3.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 355, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Nerdificent co-host Ify Nwadiwe to discuss Papa John being replaced by Shaq, Schraderbräu beer from Breaking Bad coming to life, the Mueller Report being submitted, the House Democrats trying to push out any progress in the party, Democrat...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9700690040.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 67 (Best of 3/18/19-3/22/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 74 (3/18/19-3/22/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6641503716.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AOC IS SKYNET, Forrest Gump 2 3.22.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 354, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Yelling About Pâté podcast co-host Karl Hess to discuss Bill and Ted 3, Florida proposing restrictions on Felon Voting Rights Restoration bill, Joe Biden planning to run with Stacey Abrams, Mike Huckabee thinking AOC is a robot, Jared Kush...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6272942684.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Elizabeth Holmes Voice vs Tarantino Blaccent 3.21.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 353, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and podcast host Teresa Lee to discuss Woodstock 50, the <em>Once Upon A Time In Hollywood</em> trailer, Trump continuing to attack John McCain, the new EPA administrator Andrew Wheeler's first interview, concertina wire being stolen from the ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3903168779.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Soda IS Bad? Mom, Twitter Is Deep Stating Me!! 3.20.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 352, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Sara June to discuss how soda is bad for you, Devin Nunes suing Twitter, New Zealand come down hard on their gun control laws, Fox and Friends having dumb opinions on everything as usual, MoviePass coming back, a check in with the GoFundMe hom...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4849476583.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laziness Icon Ben Carson, Captain Marvel Gives MRAs Red Pill Suppository 3.19.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 351, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jamie Loftus to discuss Captain Marvel continuing to kill it at the box office, Kirsten Gillibrand announcing her presidential campaign again, Ben Carson's laziness, Trump backing Jeanine Pirro, Beto bringing in the money, The Other Two, Pizza...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9350781925.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Treat Terrorism Like Terrorism, Jexodus? 3.18.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 350, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Brandon Johnson to discuss James Gunn returning to 'Guardians of the Galaxy 3,'&nbsp; what 'Jexodus' means'&nbsp; the terrorist attack in New Zealand, Trump openly supporting violent acts, American Civil War talks getting louder, Mike Pence's ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5353946712.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 66 (Best of 3/11/19-3/15/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 73 (3/11/19-3/15/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4224588187.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Beto Announces, LaCroix Death Spiral? 3.15.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 349, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Eli Olsberg to discuss Fox New's favorite type of pie, a check in with the admissions scandal, the House voting to make the Mueller Report public, Ivanka wanting to be president, Matt Whitaker's correcting what he said in his testimony, Beto O...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8269740119.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Yelp For Shook Ones, Budweiser Meat? 3.14.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 348, Jack and Miles are joined by writer and film critic Vince Mancini to discuss the top cities in the world, Budweiser's new meat line, if Joe Biden should run for president, Facebook being friendlier to Trump than we thought, Elizabeth Warren trying to regulate big tech companies, T...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5400836975.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Trump President In Marvel Universe? Pot Calls Kettle Racist 3.12.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 346, Jack and Miles are joined by Culture King's Edgar Momplaisir to discuss theories on who the president is in the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Trump's explanation for calling Tim Cook 'Tim Apple,' inappropriate comments out of the GOP this week, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES: <br><br>1....]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6660914742.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Man In The Mirror, GOP Not Anti-Anti-Semitism 3.11.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 345, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Eric Lampaert to discuss why it is so hard for people to cancel Michael Jackson, Captain Marvel breaking box office records, the sentencing of Paul Manafort, the house passing a resolution condemning anti-Semitism and anti-Muslim discriminatio...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4602564019.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 65 (Best of 3/4/19-3/8/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 72 (3/4/19-3/8/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3285233034.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mueller Fan Theories, LOL GO TO JAIL Paul Manafort 3.7.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 343, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Matt Lieb to discuss an update on the Papa John scandal, R. Kelly's interview with Gayle King, the Mueller investigation, Trump paying off Stormy Daniels cause he loves his family, Facebook screwing up AGAIN, Roger Stone screwing up AGAIN, new...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3418474627.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>QAnon Climbs The Charts, NBA Is Bawlin’ 3.6.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 342, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jamie Loftus to discuss the new Game Of Thrones trailer, the QAnon book climbing the charts, science proving anti-vaxxers wrong, the House Judiciary committee announcing investigation, the Islamophobic rhetoric in our government, Kanye West's ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2164147867.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>#1 King Of All Fun, Lil Tay OK? 3.4.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 340, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Hana Michels to discuss Instagram flexer Lil Tay breaking her silence, CPAC being a conservative open mic, Meghan Markle and Prince Harry choosing to raise their child with fluid approach, the man Trump hired to bid on his portrait, Sean Hanni...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2840612752.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 64 (Best of 2/25/19-3/1/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 71 (2/25/19-3/1/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7242607233.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BiTo 2020, Worst Best Picture Oscars 3.1.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 339, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Atsuko Okatsuka to discuss a mobsters thoughts on if Michael Cohen will survive prison, possible presidential run announcements from Beto and Biden, what is going on between India and Pakistan, Trump's summit with Kim Jong Un, a check in with ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7784028991.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>cOhEN iS A LiAr tHo!!! Got Beer? 2.28.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 338, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jason Burke and our local counsel Lauren Manso to discuss a man tea bagging some salsa, Representative Matt Gaetz's thoughts on Michael Cohen, Cohen's testimony, Trump's banning some journalists from his meeting with Kim Jong Un, a directors c...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9730634617.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ivanka GETS IT, Both Sides-ing Science 2.27.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 337, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss R. Kelly posting bail, McDonald's Spicy McChicken sandwich, Colorado attempting to change the electoral college system, Michael Cohen testifying against Trump, an update on the state of emergency situation, Trump's...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2263918711.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Oscars So … Bearable, So Hanoi-ing 2.26.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 336, Miles and special guest host are joined by The Daily Zeitgeist co-host Jack O'Brien to discuss R. Kelly's indictment, Trump kissing a campaign staffer without her consent, the Academy Awards, Trump's upcoming meeting with Kim Jong Un, Donald Trump Jr.'s problems with Twitter, how ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6514772931.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is It Mueller Time? Space Jam Save Us 2.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 335, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by actor and <em>Winnetka</em> podcast host Jessica Harper to discuss Steve King planning to run again, Times Up CEO resigning over her son's misconduct, Space Jam 2, the Mueller report coming soon, Michael Cohen testifying soon...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8195850762.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SMH Jussie, All Hail The Margarita 2.22.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 334, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian Blake Wexler to discuss Taco Bell's new Rattlesnake Fries, the case of Jussie Smollet, the white nationalist Coast Guard, interns being threatened with NDA's at the White House, the son of Republican congressional ca...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6410695846.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LGBTrump, RIP Space Farce 2.21.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 333, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian and scam queen Laci Mosley to discuss people trolling Captain Marvel, Emma Thompson leaving a project involving John Lasseter, Ariana Grande's zamboni past, a student selling drugs through a mobile gaming app, the Tr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3048860988.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Posthumously Canceled, LET MALIA LIVE 2.20.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 332, Miles and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian and musician Chris Crofton to discuss the Peanut Butter Pump, the death of Karl Lagerfeld, Bernie Sanders announcing his presidential run, Roger Stone being a moron, the press snitching on Malia Obama, John Wayne mak...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1202319477.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>So(ber)cial Media, The Great Fry Debate 2.19.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 331, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Kenny DeForest to discuss how millennials are drinking less cause of social media, official French fries rankings, Trump's physical exams results, Trump's state of emergency announcement, Andrew McCabe's revealing information on Jeff Sessions ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1180127722.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 62 (Best of 2/11/19-2/15/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 69 (2/11/19-2/15/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5747228619.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Of The Fail, Nike Crushes Small Businessman 2.15.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 330, Jack and Miles are joined by Yo Is This Racist's co-host Andrew Ti to discuss a Colorado store closing down after they boycotted Nike cause of Colin Kaepernick ad, Amazon canceling their plans to build an HQ in New York City, Trump calling a state of emergency over the border wall...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7393678145.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Make Executive Time Fun Again; AVATAR IS REALISTIC, STFU 2.14.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 329, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Blair Socci to discuss new innovations in indulgence, American's not being able to pay back their car loans, Trump's new golf simulator, a current day measles outbreak, Ihlan Oman's comments about AIPAC, GOP removing Colin Kaepernick's name fr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9266171996.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Finish What Wall? Pretty Sure El Chapo Did It 2.13.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 328, Miles and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian Tiff Stevenson to discuss 21 Savage's release, the trial of El Chapo, Ralph Northam's lack of knowledge, Cardi B drama, the Senate Intel Committee finding “no direct evidence” of Russian/Trump conspiracy, Trump's new ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6672397625.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Genie Body Is Goals, Coke’s Being Thirsty 2.12.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 327, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Kimia Behpoornia to discuss the new Aladdin trailer, Coke's new flavor in 10 years, a nasty Fox and Friends host, Denver teachers going back on strike, Amy Klobachar entering the presidential race, the Green New Deal, how people across the Uni...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3201688582.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MoviePass Going Strong? Bezos vs. The National Enquirer 2.11.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 327, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Sports Without Balls podcast host Erin Foley to discuss James Dolan's band, activists looking to find more racist imagery in politicians' yearbooks, Matthew Whitaker testifying before the Judiciary Committee, Jeff Bezos being extorted by A...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3933602724.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 61 (Best of 2/4/19-2/8/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 68 (2/4/19-2/8/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9811496361.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NYPD vs Waze, 21 Being Treated Savagely 2.8.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 326, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Katia Kvinge to discuss how the NYPD wants Waze to stop snitching on them, Campbell's soup trying to own the word "chunky," the new Beetlejuice Broadway musical, the truth behind 21 Savage's ICE detention, Tucker Carlson's thoughts on economic...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9831887998.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Virginia Is For Lovers (of Blackface), Netflix Won’t Chill 2.7.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 325, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and musician Chris Crofton to discuss Joshua Trump's appearance at the State Of The Union, a refrigerdating service to match you up with your soulmate, Netflix making their own <em>Planet Earth</em>, more politicians caught in black face, mill...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1799247525.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SOTU: Tiffany Trump Gets It White, Millennials Killing Inequality Industry 2.6.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 324, Jack and Miles are joined by Billy Wayne Davis to discuss some internet ads coming up, Google searches from different VPN's around the world, Trump's State Of The Union, federal prosecutors looking into Trump's inauguration committee, more Howard Schultz crap, Fox News hosts being...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8300829439.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>President Hamberder Is V Busy, Moonwalker Shocker 2.5.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 323, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and frequent podcast guest and Bechdel Cast co-host Jamie Loftus to discuss Super Bowl ads, Ralph Northam's black face controversy, an insider leaking President Trump's schedule, the White House ending intel briefings with Trump, Liam Neeson's...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1639492305.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Mueller Can’t Save Us From Schultz, ‘Ariana’ Means ‘Idiot’ In Japanese 2.1.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 321, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and artist Anna Salinas to discuss the Rams male cheerleaders making history at the Super Bowl, the half time show analysis, the Mueller probe apparently coming to a close soon, Howard Schultz comments on his CNN interview, disappointing follo...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3089836528.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KFCheeto’s, Gwyneth Paltrow: Ski Bully 1.31.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 320, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Marcella Arguello to discuss the polar vortex, the attack of Jussie Smollett, Gwyneth Paltrow's ski slope hit and run, Howard Schultz's presidential talk around town, Ariana Grande's tattoo, KFC's new Cheeto fried chicken sandwich, Justin Bieb...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2236799278.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2 Cold 2 Breathe, Wokest Dude Awards 1.30.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 319, Jack and Miles are joined by Smart Mouth podcast host Katherine Spiers to discuss the all time coldest temperatures hitting the country, the FaceTime bug allowing users to eavesdrop, the government shutdown slowing down the investigation into the Trump administration, Black Panthe...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5087249811.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jason Momoa = Universal Truth, Pretty Petty Presidential Petulance 1.29.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 318, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Blake Wexler to discuss the DC film <em>Aquaman</em> surpassing <em>The Dark Night</em> in the box office, the 2020 vision that has Democrats shook, an inside look at White House tours with Trump as president, Trump's anger at the state run me...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6607348547.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Roger Stone Is Totally Screwed, Kim Kardashian Runs These Dudes 1.28.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 317, Jack and and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian Nick Turner to discuss The Game's new song about Kim Kardashian, Roger Stone's indictment, how the United States helped screw over Venezuela, Facebook connecting WhatsApp, FB Messaging, and Instagram, and more! Als...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1493572056.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 59 (Best of 1/22/19-1/25/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 66 (1/22/19-1/25/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3633367320.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wilbur Ross Doesn’t Speak POOR, Zuckerberg Develops Taste For Blood 1.25.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 316, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Brooke Van Poppelen to discuss the adjective "wild," Mark Zuckerberg's meat obsession, the State Of The Union being delayed, the situation in Venezuela, Wilbur Ross's lack of understanding of the human race, Costco's new streaming-video servic...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1389536737.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Giuliani Drunk Driving The News Cycle? The Kids Are All White 1.24.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 315, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Lydia Popovich to discuss McDonalds new bacon happy hour, the Sweetheart shortage, Trump abandoning a State Of The Union at the House for elsewhere, the Trump administrations annoyance at Rudy Giuliani, the support for Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3905375966.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fyre Festival Sociopaths, Trump’s Photoshopping Himself 1.23.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 314, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Pat Sirois to discuss the Super Bowl, the Fyre Festival documentaries, Trump releasing photoshopped photos of himself, Supreme Court upholding Trump's military trans ban, the Fox News graphic declaring the incorrect death of Ruth Bader Ginsbur...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4784206618.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Made Cohen Do Lies? THE Personality Test 1.22.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 313, Jack and Miles are joined by Disgraceland host Jake Brennan to discuss FiveThirtyEight's personality quiz, Democrats' 2020 nominees, Trump directing Michael Cohen to lie to congress for him, William Barr's confirmation hearing, the speculation on what will end government shutdown,...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9249682568.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 58 (Best of 1/14/19-1/18/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 65 (1/14/19-1/18/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3977680630.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN’s Bias Against AOC, Ohhh RUSSIAN Collusion 1.17.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 312, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Zainab Johnson to discuss Dick Run Claire, a new Trump-inspired <em>Space Force</em> comedy from <em>The Office</em> creators, Rudy Giuliani claiming he never said 'no collusion,' Michael Cohen paying an IT firm to appear likable, Alexandria O...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4487320404.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Late Life With Mike Huckabee, Netflix And Bill 1.17.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 311, Jack and Miles are joined by Yo Is This Racist host Andrew Ti to discuss the new Gillette ad, Mike Huckabee's new weekly show, Brexit and Theresa May surviving the no-confidence vote, Trump losing support, Karen Pence's new job at an anti-LGBTQ school, Travis Scott and Big Boi agr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5765896236.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohhh WHITE Supremacy, Best TV Dramas Since Sopranos 1.16.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 310, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Tamer Kattan to discuss the best television shows since <em>The Sopranos</em>, William Barrs memo on the Mueller investigation, Trump's dinner for the Clemson crew, Republicans coming for Steve King's racist comments, how sex offender and paed...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7491748202.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trend Alert: Escape Room Murder, Egg Is OUT HERE 1.15.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 309, Jack and Miles are joined by Reality Bytes co-host Courtney Kocak to discuss fake news about The Rock, the weekend box office, Trump's popularity level, Mueller looking into Trump's working relationship with Russia, the LA Unified School District going on strike, the egg that won ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6909608980.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dwayne “The Right” Johnson, Wall &gt; Wheel? 1.14.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[<br>In episode 308, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Amy Miller to discuss how The Rock is a few more quotes away from being a Fox News pundit, Mueller putting the final touches on the report, Trump's iron clad wall argument, the Jayme Closs story, Coming To America 2 and more!<br><br><br>FO...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7756397012.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 57 (Best of 1/7/19-1/11/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 64 (1/7/19-1/11/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6689244313.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RIP MacKenzie Bezos’ DMs, Trump Shutdown Survival Guide 1.11.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 307, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Candice Thompson to discuss the Bezos divorce, the government shutdown continuing and the Trump Administrations lack of understanding about it, Steve King's idiotic comments about white nationalism, the prediction that the US will drop to the ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6397375457.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Collusion No Longer An Illusion, Manafort Lawyers Self-Own 1.10.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 306, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and writer Carmen Angelica to discuss Woodstock 2019, Paul Manafort and the Trump Administration's collusion with Russia, the stuff discussed in Trump's press conference this week, Angela Davis losing a civil rights award for boycotting Israel...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1836867125.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Millennials Ruining Exhaustion, Mike Pence School Of Bad Improv 1.9.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 305, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Megan Gailey to discuss the burnout generation, Trump's lack of knowledge about how the government shut down goes who it impacts, the continuous push for a border wall by the right, the lie Trump told about Syria, Kevin Spacey's delusional com...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6710870903.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>R&amp;B Predator(s?), More like Bohemian Crap-City 1.8.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 304, Jack and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by comedian Casey Ley to discuss the R. Kelly docuseries, Cynthoia Brown being granted clemency, the video of Drake bringing an underage woman on stage, the sonic attacks in Havana, the Golden Globes, Kevin Hart's lack of an apolo...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3790972823.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MF’er Gate, Mary Poppinsganda 1.7.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 303, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss a certain Bachelor contestant who has gone viral, Ellen pushing Kevin Hart to host the Oscars, Representative Rashida Tlaib's comments about Trump, the R.Kelly docuseries, the Golden Globes, Mary Poppins leaving it...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3230240905.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 56 (Best of 12/31/18-1/4/19)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 63 (12/31/18-1/4/19.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7911666904.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bird Box Office Bonanza, Conservatives Catch Woman Dancing 1.4.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 302, Jack and special guest host Jamie Loftus is joined by comedian Caitlin Durante in this Bechdal Cast take over to discuss the Bird Box challenge, the Masked Singer television show, the video of Alexandra Ocasio-Cortez that has offended conservatives, all the women who were sworn in...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6706342752.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Louis C(old ta)K(es), Twinning App Makes Dystopia Fun 1.3.19</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 301, Jack and special guest host Ever Mainard are joined by comedian Jenny Zigrino to discuss Kanye West and Kim Kardashian expecting baby number four, Kanye's anger at Drake, Louis CK's new problematic comedy set, Popsugar's Twinning app leaking people's photos, Trump's pseudo-press c...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9689650800.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>One Hundred Percent Accurate Predictions for 2019</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In this new year, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Laci Mosley and super producer Anna Hossnieh to make some super accurate predictions for the year of 2019.&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcas...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9690916182.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2018 Year End Lists In Review 12.31.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 300, Jack and special guest co-host Jamie Loftus are joined by comedian Yusef Roach to discuss defining events from the year: Walmart's bizarre top selling items in 2018, Time's person of the year list, Google trends from the year, top box office reports from the year, best films of th...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8312370082.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 Of Everything 2018</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In this bonus holiday episode, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss their top five EVERYTHINGS!&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4153098606.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Underrated Things of 2018</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In this holiday underrated spectacular, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Alison Stevenson and super producer Anna Hossnieh to talk about all the things they found underrated in the 2018 year!&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertise...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6425115018.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Overrated Things of 2018</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In this Overrated holiday extravaganza, Jack and Miles and joined by comedian and Reality Bytes podcast co-host Sofiya Alexandra and super producer Anna Hossnieh to discuss all the overrated aspects of the 2018 year.&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.c...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7261421802.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily Zeitgeist Presents: Santa University Part 2</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[It's that time of year again! Join Jamie Loftus, Caitlin Durante, Edgar Momplaisir, Anna Hossnieh, Shereen Younes, Jack O'Brien, Miles Gray, Robert Evans, Jacquis Neal, Sophie Lichterman, and Anna Salinas as they do a table read of Santa University, part two!&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6152732476.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Noted Hotness Expert Michael Rapaport, Trump Hiding Bad News In The Holidays? 12.21.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 299, Jack and special guest host Jamie Loftus are joined by Daniel and Jorge Explain the Universe hosts Daniel Whiteson and Jorge Cham to discuss Michelle Obama's Balenciaga boots, Michael Rapaport's comments about Ariana Grande, Trump's decision on Syria, women leaving Trump's camp, a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4493651452.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>President Christmas-Movie-Villain, Giuliani May Just Be Drunk 12.20.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 298, Jack and Miles are joined by Stuff You Should Know co-host and The End Of The World host Josh Clark to discuss Twitter trends including Will Smith as the Genie, the Carlton dance coming from Bruce Springsteen,&nbsp; Paul Ryan's final speech, James Harden, some more absurd Rudy Giu...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3097806298.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Day Of L’s, Carlton Makes ‘Em Pay 12.19.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 297, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Alison Stevenson to discuss a new advertisement asking people to give Trump some love, the Trump administration's weird attempts to raise money, Michael Flynn's delayed sentencing, the dissolution of the Trump Foundation, how Russian social me...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1270074562.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Poutine = Salad? CBS = Continuous Bull S*** 12.18.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 296, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss Washington Post's wild claim that a hot dog is not a sandwich, KFC's fried chicken fire logs, Rudy Giuliani's dumb defense of Trump's crimes, Ryan Zinke's resignation, CBS paying off Eliza Dushku cause of her haras...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7865026453.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Instagram: Where Love Lives, Asbestos? A**ButtStuff! 12.17.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 295, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Laci Mosley to discuss Instagram's year in review, an Instagram influencer's scam, Rudy Giuliani's thoughts on Trump's crimes, a child dying of dehydration while in ICE custody, shady behavior by Johnson &amp; Johnson, Postmates starting to us...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7176632289.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 54 (Best of 12/10/18-12/14/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 61 (12/10/18-12/14/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9832331737.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Netflix For Real? Dude Looks Like A Robot 12.14.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 294, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian the Reality Bytes podcast co-host Sofiya Alexandra to discuss a 'high-tech' robot in Russia that's just a man in a costume, earthquakes in the Midwest, Trump's love for Adderall, David Pecker and AMI flipping on Trump, the Senate passing a res...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3005875512.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Keto Is King, Too-Early 2020 Dem Nominee Polls 12.13.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 293, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Sara June to discuss the most Googled foods, a preview of the 2020 candidates, the Google CEO sitting down to testify in front of congress, the fall out of the Trump/Pelosi/Schumer showdown, the silence of Mike Pence, Michael Cohen going to pr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1955116007.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wall Til You Fall, Gig Economy Is KILLING It 12.12.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 292, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Sara Schaefer to discuss Nicki Minaj defending another sex offender, the business of location based tracking, Trump's showdown with Nancy Pelosi over the border wall, deaths that have occurred at Airbnb's, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES:<br><br>1...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5899436124.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Worse Job: Oscar Host Or Trump Chief Of Staff? Steph Curry: Moon Hoaxer 12.11.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 291, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Paige Weldon to discuss Steph Curry's theory on the moon landing, two jobs we can't fill in the US (Oscars host AND White House Chief of Staff), the failing of an Alt-right convention, Russian spy Matina Butina possibly flipping, Individual 1 ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3754194994.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 53 (Best of 12/3/18-12/7/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 60 (12/3/18-12/7/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1664022261.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Laws = Low Approval Ratings, John Krasinski Was ROBBED! 12.7.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 289, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Kyle Ayers to discuss Trump blaming Mueller for his low approval rating, Trump eyeing his new attorney general, Tucker Carlson coming for Trump, Saudi Arabia helping out Trump's hotels, Golden Globe nominations, Kevin Hart's twitter controvers...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8564548393.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pre-Mueller Report Jitters, Insane Doctors Suggest 6 Fries Limit 12.6.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 288, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Guy Montgomery to discuss Fortnite emotes attracting lawsuits, the break up of Cardi B and Offset, Trump and Michael Cohen's obstruction of justice, the right trying to downplay the Mueller investigation, more on the North Carolinas voter frau...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3132505872.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Smoking Saw, Shop Til THEY Drop 12.5.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 287, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and frequent podcast guest Jamie Loftus to discuss a dating app for the right, how Netflix figuring out how to keep Friends on their streaming service, the White House correcting Trump's comments on the trade wars with China, how Robert Muelle...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7869895107.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nerds Settle Movie Debate With Science, One Grande Iced Ariana Please 12.4.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 286, Jack and Miles are joined by Behind the Bastards host Robert Evans to discuss bronze Nick Offerman, Ariana Grande's music video "Thank U, Next," the death of George H.W. Bush, aggressive voter fraud in North Carolina, the most influential films, directors, and actors of all time a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4713934283.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 52 (Best of 11/26/18-11/30/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 59 (11/26/18-11/30/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7382771070.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Cohen, Cohen, Gone; Can We Eat That Giant Cow? 11.30.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 284, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Blair Socci to discuss more shady Les Moonves behavior, accusations of misconduct against Tom Brokaw, a quick look at how Alexander Acosta helped cover Jeffrey Epstein's crimes, Michael Cohen's guilty plea, the mess that is Trump's network, th...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5993304176.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bolton Not Fluent In Empathy, Rudolph The Red-Nosed Victim 11.29.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 283, Jack and Miles are joined by writer and performer Katy Stoll to discuss the darkness of the classic Christmas movie "Rudolph The Red Nosed Reindeer," more of Paul Manafort's shady behavior, John Bolton's excuse for not listening to the Jamal Khashoggi murder tapes, Fuller House se...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8403041887.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Exorcisms Are Up! Netflix For Birthers 11.28.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 282, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jono Zalay to discuss Fox New's new Netflix: Fox Nation, evil percolating in the zeitgeist, Trump bragging that he blow's Ronald Reagan away, Scott Pruitt working with 'Fox and Friends' to control the narrative when it came to his appearances,...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8017227782.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nacho Dad’s Pepper Spray, Mueller Report To Be LIT 11.27.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 281, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Alison Stevenson to discuss the weekend box office, Melania's White House Christmas decorations, the Mueller Report coming out soon, the US climate report, the situation with the immigrants seeking asylum at the Mexico/US border, Jerry Springe...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8750479450.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Left-Overs, Unders, Myths</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[What's overrated? What's underrated? What's your Google search? You have a myth?? Tell it like it is! Comedian Teresa Lee and super producer Anna Hossnieh join Jack and Miles to get down on some leftovers on this special Black Friday bonus episode.&nbsp;<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8204874309.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lunchables: Ciggs For Kids, Pelosi Not Scared 11.21.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 279, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Teresa Lee to discuss the weekly Google trends skim, a deeper look at the attack on diplomats in Cuba, Democrats gripe with Nancy Pelosi, the 30th anniversary of Lunchables, Thanksgiving plans, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES:<br><br>1. <a href="h...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7405110724.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Colin Jost: Working Class Hero, How To Ruin McDonald’s Fries 11.20.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 278, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Nick Turner to discuss an Instagram mother shouting out her son his birthday, new Cheesy Bacon Fries at McDonalds, criticism Colin Jost is receiving for his comments about Amazon HQ coming to New York, plus a call with Jose Ortiz Jr., Executiv...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5197030136.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lawrence: Mexican Icon, The Weed Bubble Is Here 11.19.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 277, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Yusef Roach to discuss an essay on fake Australian accents, Dior and Jennifer Lawrence being accused of cultural appropriation, the White House agreeing to reinstate Jim Acosta's press pass, marijuana prices falling, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTE...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9911992718.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 50 (Best of 11/12/18-11/16/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 57 (11/12/18-11/16/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8710643191.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Facebook Is Trash Part 6,997; XO Fake Tour Life 11.16.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 276, Jack and Miles are joined by Yo Is This Racist? podcast host Andrew Ti to discuss a fake band who booked a European tour, Michael Avenatti's questionable arrest, Melania's dismissed of Mira Ricardel from the White House, votes in Florida being disqualified over mismatched signatur...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7195984069.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Big D Toilet, Small D Energy; If A Mid Life Crisis Were A Toy 11.15.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 275, Jack and Miles are joined by Doctor Mister Cody Johnston to discuss our acting attorney general's working for a company that hawks weird products, conspiracy theories for why Fox News still hasn't tweeted, Trump continuing to throw a tantrum over his weekend, the right giving Demo...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8927308693.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NRA vs Legitimate Science, Keurig ‘Cept For Booze 11.14.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 274, Jack and Miles are joined by Creature Feature host Katie Goldin to discuss sugar-monitoring groups coming for milkshakes with over a thousand calories, Tucker Carlson's lies, Trump's France trip going poorly, Melania demanding a security aide be fired, the NRA's beef with medical ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4241606899.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Papa John Go Away, Stan Lee Come Back! 11.13.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 273, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jamie Loftus to discuss Stan Lee's passing, NYC's Pink Tax for female commuters, California's largest wildfires to date, the lack of caravan talk now that the midterms are over, the blue wave making its way, the lack of funds in the GOP, Toy S...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5719637444.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sad Boy Tucker, Already With The Xmas Music? 11.12.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 272, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Eric Lampaert to discuss the weekend box office, Ice-T never having eaten a bagel, China's new AI journalists, Trump claiming he doesn't know new acting attorney general Matt Whitaker, a look at Tucker Carlson's life, bloidwatch, and more! <br...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1236279500.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 49 (Best of 11/5/18-11/9/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 56 (11/5/18-11/9/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8493075167.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>R(U)(S)si(A), Oprah’s Favorite Things (For Rich Slobs) 11.9.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 271, Jack and Miles are joined by podcaster Yusong Liu to discuss RBG's fall, the White House releasing a doctored video to attack Jim Acosta, Trump's attempt to push back on the Mueller investigation by making his friend the acting attorney general, another mass shooting in America, t...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4047013761.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This (Jeff) Session’s Over, Chasing The Perfect Wave 11.8.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 270, Jack and Miles are joined by writer Jason Pargin to discuss Jeff Session's resignation, Rod Rosenstein leaving the Mueller probe, Trump's post-election press conference, voter demographics in the context of higher education, a Breaking Bad movie, most Googled Thanksgiving foods, a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5439999639.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Wave-ish, Sandler’s Still Got It 11.7.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 269, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Sofiya Alexandra to discuss Adam Sandler's new Netflix special, midterm elections, the GOP's list of things they need to respond to once the Democrats take the house, aliens, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES: <br><br>1. <a href="https://junkee.com/...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6247898541.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Queen Of The Zeitgeist, What To Worry About On Election Day 11.6.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 268, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and host of the Alchemy This! podcast Kevin Pollak to discuss the Bohemian Rhapsody film, Trump's behavior during midterms, Brian Kemp's office investigating the Democrats, why people like death metal, the calming game of Tetris, and more! <br...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4301232766.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah vs Fox, Real Housewives Of The Vatican 11.5.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 267, Jack and Miles are joined by writer, activist, and co-host of the #GoodMuslimBadMuslim podcast Tanzila "Taz" Ahmed to discuss Fox News being annoyed at Oprah for getting involved in Georgia, the UK possibly changing laws because too many people getting wasted at the airport, Niger...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5215658940.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 48 (Best of 10/29/18-11/2/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 55 (10/29/18-11/2/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4425958715.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah Vs. Pence, RIP ‘Cado Toast 11.2.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 266, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss crazy Red Sox fans throwing full beer cans, trending Halloween costumes, Oprah's face off with Mike Pence in Georgia, Jacob Wohl and Jack Burkman's press conference regarding the women accusing Robert Mueller of ha...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3817958762.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah vs Voter Suppression, It’s Too Late Kanye 11.1.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 265, Miles and special guest co-host Jamie Loftus are joined by writer and performer Sarah Isaacson to discuss Kanye West's claim to be back from the sunken place, Trumps trip to Pittsburgh and his continued hate speech, the poorly planned plot to discredit Robert Mueller by Jacob Wohl...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3665681086.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Right’s Even Tired Of Fox News, Lena Dunham To Go Full Lohan? 10.31.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[Boo! In episode 264, Jack and Miles are joined by writer and Hollywood Handbook podcast co-host Hayes Davenport to discuss how villains in horror movies rarely use guns, Matt Drudge being fed up with Fox News, how a convicted man for anti-Muslim terror plot blaming Trump for his actions, how in t...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5350396376.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jekyll and Himmler, WTF Is Blexit? 10.30.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 263, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Noah Gardenswartz to discuss Kanye's West's new 'blexit' stance, the Indonesian plane crash, the Pittsburgh synagogue shooting, whether the mainstream media will start acknowledging the blatant racism in this country, Brazil's new far-right pr...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2567017973.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Maga Bomber Parody Of Himself, Bieber Burrito Saga A False Flag? 10.29.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 262, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Vanessa Gritton to discuss Justin Bieber's lack of burrito eating skills, a suspect being arrested in connection to the mail bombs, the inevitable cries of crisis actors and false flags, the dog that tricks people into giving her McDonald's, t...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2028738113.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The News Is A Tarantino Film, Make Groping Legal Again 10.24.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 259, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Brandon Johnson to discuss 2018 being the year of costumes for black children, Megyn Kelly's thoughts on black face, updates on the Jamal Khashoggi murder, the caravan that is scaring the right, Trump's new idea to give the middle class a tax ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4187664453.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Low Effort Topical Costumes, Why Horror Will Look Insane In 200 Years 10.23.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 258, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Marlena Rodriguez to discuss how the new Halloween film killed the box office over the weekend, the Trump administration trying to eliminate the definition of 'transgender,' Chipotle's 'Boo-rito' discount, UberEats considering delivering food ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7197721449.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna To NFL: Na Fam, Four Loko For Rich Whites 10.22.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 257, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Eric Lampaert to discuss a new cold brew with alcohol, how Netflix is finally starting to cancel shows, John Kelly and John Bolton's shouting match about immigration, the GOP taking up it's racism a notch with a new robo-call, the right's smea...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6294786325.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 46 (Best of 10/15/18-10/19/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 53 (10/15/18-10/19/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8351303314.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Whole Cruz World, Resource Warz! 10.19.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 256, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Julian McCullough to discuss a profile on Heidi Cruz, Ted Cruz's wife, Facebook's inflated video metrics, the boost of racism in the GOP, how a group of black senior citizens were ordered off a Georgia bus taking them to vote, the mainstream m...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2984203016.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Julian Assange: Worst House Guest, The Murderer’s Story Checks Out 10.18.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 255, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Danielle Radford to discuss Julian Assange being the worst <br>asylum seeking couch surfer, more info on the murder of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi, The Turning Point group's problem with hiring racists, Mueller getting ready to give us so...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8844262039.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hollywood’s Longest Continuous Bender, Demo(n)crats 10.17.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 254, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Nick Vatterott to discuss Google trends with Amy Winehouse, Tara Reid, Lady Gaga's fiancé Christian Carino, and Nathan Fillion, a culture wars report, Tucker Carlson crying, the right believing in black magic, the push for a civil war, the NYP...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3820436673.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>R.I.P.ete and Ariana, Psych! Rogue Killer 10.16.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 253, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Ryan Singer to discuss the break up of Pete Davidson and Ariana Grande, Meghan Markle's pregnancy, Trump's 60 Minutes interview, Elizabeth Warren's ancestry, Saudi Arabia possibly copping to killing journalist Jamal Khashoggi, the most and lea...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6299324926.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alexa, Was My Life Good? JFK: Solved! 10.15.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 252, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Bechdel Cast host Caitlin Durante to discuss new Amazon Echo devices, how Amazon found a way to screw over their warehouse workers, Trump wanting to replace Nikki Haley with a woman because of Kavanaugh, the fact that we are due for anothe...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2934854169.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 45 (Best of 10/8/18-10/12/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 52 (10/8/18-10/12/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3656680282.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Not Sure How Movies Work, Hail Little Caesar 10.12.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 251, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian, Pop Culture Collaborative fellow, and #GoodMuslimBadMuslim co-host Zahra Noorbakhsh to discuss Google trends, Kanye West's meeting with Trump at the White House, how Georgia's Secretary of State Brian Kemp is blocking over 50k voter registrat...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3177728602.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Melania “Hot Take” Trump, These 100 Companies Killed The Planet 10.11.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 250, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Reality Bytes co-host Sofiya Alexandra to discuss Hurricane Michael, Melania Trump's comments on the #metoo movement, Trump's mis-leading op-ed on Medicare-For-All, the right fearing for their lives cause of liberals, Trump's behavior lead...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4902466534.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Admin’s Only Popular Member Quits, 12 Years Left? 10.10.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 249, Jack and Miles are joined by visual artist and The Soft Spot co-host Meg Molloy to discuss the effects of Taylor Swift's political post, Kanye West's meeting with Trump, the false narrative that the republicans outmaneuvered the democrats, Nikki Haley's resignation, the fact that ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3936118148.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox: KANYE &gt; TAYLOR SWIFT, Banksy Banksy’s It Up On A Banksy 10.9.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 248, Jack and Miles are joined by Kinda Dating podcast host Natasha Chandel to discuss website traffic rankings, Venom and A Star Is Born crushing the box office, a new story that reveals that dogs aren't as smart as we thought, Taylor Swift finally getting political, all the state dea...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5820404548.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Collins: Feminist ICON, Hooters Going Extinct 10.8.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 247, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian, writer, and You're Making It Worse podcast co-host H. Alan Scott to discuss Russian bots entering the culture wars, Krispy Kreme coming to Ireland, the film A Star Is Born with super producer Anna Hossnieh, Susan Collins decision to vote for ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2131257963.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 44 (Best of 10/1/18-10/5/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 51 (10/1/18-10/5/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2224537615.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Killer Selfie! Republicans Energized By Assault 10.5.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 246, Jack and Miles are joined by writer and Reality Bytes podcast host Courtney Kocak to discuss Chris Evan's retiring as the role of Captain America, updates on the Kavanaugh investigation, selfies causing deaths, how hugs can make you happier, the city of Houston trying to shut down...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6309815741.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Most Hated Foods, Trump’s Self-Made Myth 10.4.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 245, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Jamie Loftus to discuss the 'Presidential Alert' text message American's received, Adam McKay's new film about Dick Cheney and the Bush Administration, how Trump's brand is suffering since he entered the White House, the GOP's lack of care for...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5975777234.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>UBoof40’s, Bezos Blesses The Peasants 10.3.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 244, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Liz Stewart to discuss Comedy Cellar's new policy cause of Louis CK, more news from Kavanaugh's wild drinking days, how the Trumps think this is a scary time for white men, how Whole Foods employees are considering unionizing since Amazon acqu...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9208224058.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How About St. Lohan, Kanye For President (Of The Sunken Place) 10.2.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 243, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Yusef Roach to discuss Lindsay Lohan's weird white savior behavior on Instagram Live, Kanye West's appearance on SNL, Pete Davidson and his sex life, how the FBI investigation into Kavanaugh is going, Elon Musk stepping down as chairman of Tes...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9905414601.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Lit The Fuse, Facebook Breach #49,587 10.1.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 242, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and activist Derrick Lemos to discuss Olive Garden's new lasagna dip, Facebook being breached, more on the Kavanaugh testimony and the delayed vote on the senate floor, a possible civil war in our future, the SEC suing Elon Musk, bloidwatch, a...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8574132101.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 43 (Best of 9/24/18-9/28/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 50 (9/24/18-9/28/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1149907854.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kavanaugh Testimony: WTF Was That? 9.28.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 241, Jack and Miles are joined by comedians Jamie Loftus and Noah Gardenswartz to discuss Dr. Christine Blasey Ford's testimony, Brett Kavanaugh's testimony, the Steak Umm's Twitter account going off, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES: <br><br>1. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-ne...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6283420220.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brett-Ghazi, The Worst Candy Ever (Has Been Saved) 9.27.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 240, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Go Fact Yourself co-host's Helen Hong to discuss the real reason Bradley Cooper decided to make 'A Star Is Born,' Necco Wafers and Sweethearts being saved from candy extinction, Rod Rosenstein's big meeting with Trump, a new accuser coming...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6229050716.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeremy Renner’s Weird Secret Life, Ted Cruz Meets The World 9.26.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 240, Jack and Miles are joined by writer, performer, and You're Making It Worse co-host Eliot Glazer to discuss Jeremy Renner's hobbies, Lil Xan overdosing on Flaming Hot Cheetos, a hundred year old man receiving Chick-Fil-A for life, Ted Cruz and his wife being heckled out of a restau...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW5175289056.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Be(elzebub)yonce, It REALLY WAS Russia 9.25.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 239, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and co-host of the You're Making It Worse podcast Brent Sullivan to discuss Beyonce's drummer claiming Bey is a witch and controlling her, Rod Rosenstein's upcoming meeting with Trump, more accusations about Brett Kavanaugh that came out, a ne...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2157496721.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Grandpa Is High AF, Michael Moore = Trump of The Left 9.24.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 238, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Caleb Synan to discuss who will be playing the Super Bowl halftime show, how baby boomers are more likely to smoke weed these days, Michael Cohen flipping on Trump, Rod Rosenstein apparently trying to figure out a way to evoke the 25th Amendme...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6930042153.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 42 (Best of 9/17/18-9/21/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 49 (9/17/18-9/21/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9311647933.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Breh Kavanaugh, That New Spider-Man Game Tho 9.21.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 237, Jack and Miles are joined by New Player Has Joined podcast hosts Keith Kingbay and Jesse Neil to discuss the new Spider Man game, Trump thinking you can build a wall across the Sahara, more Kavanaugh information, conspiracy theories the right is spreading about Dr. Christine Blase...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW4654413448.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hurricane Free Yacht, Scooters Are The New Velocipede 9.20.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 236, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Ryan Singer to discuss Kylie Jenner's first experience with cereal and milk, the new Space Jam sequel that was announced, more on the Kavanaugh situation, whether or not Bert and Ernie were in a loving relationship, Sony re-releasing the PlayS...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3626329110.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>YETI Persisted, MAGA = Mushrooms Are Genitals, Actually 9.19.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 235, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Billy Wayne Davis to discuss Trump's penis, what conservatives are saying about the sexual assault accusations against Kavanaugh, the Emmy's, Elon Musk's new money guy, Sean Penn's thought's on #MeToo, and more! <br><br>FOOTNOTES: <br><br>1. <...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW1055932364.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Brett Kavanaugh: Mayor Of Keg City, ‘Apprentice’ Creator Literally Fights Tom Arnold 9.18.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 234, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Wayne Federman to discuss Tom Arnold's fight with Mark Burnett, Senators on both sides delaying the vote on Kavanaugh because of the recent discovery, Trump's war against women, Roger Stone's associate Randy Credico, a new study that finds fou...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9134505177.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Flu Shot Ya? America’s Strongest Brands 9.17.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 233, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Natch Beaut Podcast host Jackie Johnson to discuss Drake's new girlfriend, Nike stock booming, Paul Manafort's decision to take a plea deal, Andrew Cuomo beating Cynthia Nixon in the New York primaries, why you should get your flu shot, ne...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9985547690.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 41 (Best of 9/10/18-9/14/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 48 (9/10/18-9/14/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW9198241278.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Wine Not? McHostile Work Environment With Cheese 9.14.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 232, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Amanda Salvatore to discuss a wine glass holder for your shower, how the Department of Homeland Security transferred millions from the Coast Guard to ICE, Trump continuing to deny the real death toll from Hurricane Maria in Puerto Rico, update...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7899889803.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Grift-eth Paltrow, Disaster Dogwhistles 9.13.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 231, Jack and Miles are joined by Culture King podcast's co-host Edgar Momplaisir to discuss Hurricane Florence updates, the Trump Administration's transferring al to of money from FEMA to ICE to detain immigrants, Paul Manafort's possible plea deals, new Trump documentaries coming out...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW8248702611.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>There You Are Lady Gaga; Wait, Ted Cruz … Sucks? 9.12.13</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 230, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Yusef Roach to discuss the new Apple iPhone releases, Cynthia Nixon's bagel of choice, the killing of Botham Jean, midterm updates with Ted Cruz and Beto O'Rourke, the passing of Mac Miller, Hurricane Florence's path, Lady Gaga's break out mom...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7078927112.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>John Legend EGOT, Les Moonves HE GONE 9.11.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 229, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Culture King's host Jacquis Neal to discuss Hurricane Florence, Les Moonves exiting CBS and his work to destroy Janet Jackson's career, a look at the effects of 9/11, the US Open Final with Serena Williams and Naomi Osaka, the woman who di...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW2269529861.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Disappears People From Rallies, Dictionary Adds New Words 9.10.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 228, Jack and special guest host Laci Mosley are joined by actor and writer Lucas Neff to discuss Barack Obama's speech at University of Illinois, Trump staffer's switching out indifferent people behind him at his rallies, how Trump wants Sessions to investigate who wrote the NY Times ...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW6098538063.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Zeitgeist 40 (Best of 9/3/18-9/7/18)</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[The weekly round up of the best moments from DZ's Season 47 (9/3/18-9/7/18.)<br><br> Learn more about your ad-choices at <a href='https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers'>https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers</a>]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW7689255738.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Goes Coup Coup, Kamala Harris Has Receipts 9.7.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 227, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian Max Silvestri to discuss Democrats grilling Brett Kavanaugh at his senate committee hearing, the death of Burt Reynolds, the New York Times anonymous op-ed piece from someone inside the Trump Administration, the normalization of Trump's corrup...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3528692594.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Alex Jones vs Rubio, Kanye vs Drake: FIGHT! 9.6.18</title><link>https://www.dailyzeitgeist.com/</link><description><![CDATA[In episode 226, Jack and Miles are joined by comedian and Bechdel Cast co-host Caitlin Durante to discuss Kanye's apology to Drake, updates from Brett Kavanaugh's senate confirmation hearing, the Marco Rubio and Alex Jones spat, how the Republican Party is shrinking, some more take aways from Bob...]]></description><author>iHeartRadio</author><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HSW3677508149.mp3" length="" type="audio/ogg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>